paddle8.com 2015-06-28

# Paddle8: Privacy Policy

Paddle8.com and GavelandGrand.com (the "Sites") are published and maintained by Paddle8, Inc. and its subsidiaries (collectively referred to as "Paddle8," "we," "us," or "our").

This Privacy Policy governs your use of the Sites. By visiting the Sites, and/or using the services offered on or through the Sites (the "Services"), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, our Terms and Conditions, which governs your use of the Sites in general.

_Purpose_

Your privacy is an important matter to us. We may ask you for Personal Information and we may collect certain information from you and your computer (about you and your interaction with the Sites) each time you visit us in order to make your visits to the Sites and use of the services available through the Sites worthwhile. "Personal Information" includes, for example, your name; title; home and/or business address; email address; home and/or business telephone and fax number; credit card and other payment information; demographic information; art interests or preferences, art purchases, offer activity, offer amounts, payment history; and/or other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online or offline contact with you as an individual. This Privacy Policy explains, in general, what Personal Information and other information is collected on the Sites, how the information is used, and with whom we may share such information.

_Opt-In and Opt-Out_

You have the right to "opt-in" and "opt-out" of certain of our uses of your Personal Information. You may request not to (1) receive correspondence from us (either on our behalf or on behalf of a third party), or (2) have your Personal Information shared with other entities for their marketing purposes, by sending us an email to opt-out@paddle8.com. In this email, please say whether: (i) you would like to opt-out of receiving promotional correspondence from Paddle8 in general, or just via email or regular mail, (ii) you would only like to opt-out of certain of Paddle8 mailings, newsletters, email alerts or other correspondence, and if so which ones, and/or (iii) you would like to elect for us not to share your Personal Information with third parties for their marketing purposes. You may also opt-out of Paddle8 promotional emails by clicking on an opt-out link within the email you receive or of Paddle8 postal mailings by following the directions in such mailings.

Please understand that if you opt-out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us. Also, a request to have us stop sharing your Personal Information with other entities for marketing purposes will only apply as of your request, and we will not be responsible for any communications that you may receive from entities that received your Personal Information prior to such request. In these cases, please contact that entity directly.

_Information collected on the Sites_

User-Provided Information. We collect Personal Information from users of the Sites through users' activities, transactions and completion of online forms. Such information may be collected when users register to become members of the Sites (for example, without limitation, when you register to look at certain items for sale, purchase lots, send us an email, or in any other way submit Personal Information to us via the Sites). We do not store or share credit card information.

_Sites’ Usage Information_

Cookies. If you have permitted your computer to accept cookies, we may use "cookies" to keep, and sometimes track, information about you. Cookies are small data files that are sent to your browser or related software from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies track where you travel on the Sites and what you look at, transact and purchase. They may store the information in your shopping cart, and/or your username and/or password, and we may use them to deliver specific messages to you. A cookie may enable us to relate your use of the Sites to other information about you, including your Personal Information. All of these purposes serve to improve and personalize your experience on the Sites.

Most Web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. Additionally, if you have a Flash player installed on your computer, your Flash player can be set to reject or delete Flash cookies. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Sites or certain areas or features of the Sites.

IP Address and Clickstream Data. Our server automatically collects data about your server's Internet address when you visit us. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or IP Address, is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you're on the Internet. When you request pages from the Sites, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Your IP Address is used to help identify you and to gather demographic information about our customers as a whole, but does not include personally identifiable information. Our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us; the pages you visit on the Sites; the other sites you visit after the Sites; the ads you see and/or click on; other information about the type of Web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on the Sites or a referral site; and other Web usage activity and data logged by our Web servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Sites. Such information may also be used to gather demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider. We may link this information with your Personal Information.

Any or all of these activities with regard to Sites Usage Information may be performed on our behalf by our services providers, including, for example, our analytics vendor(s).

_Our use of your Personal Information_

We will use the Personal Information you provide to the Sites, for example, to respond to your requests and to provide you with our product and service offerings: we will process and fulfill your purchases, respond to your requests and inquiries and provide you with the services and features offered on or through the Sites. We may also use your Personal Information to maintain our internal record keeping. We may also report information about your account to credit bureaus. Late payments, missed payments, or other defaults on your account may be reflected in your credit report. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both Personal Information and Sites’ Usage Information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including third parties. We also may compare your contact information to data in our databases in order to improve the Sites and marketing. Also, advertisements and other content displayed to you on the Sites may be customized to your interests and preferences, based on your Personal Information and Sites’ Usage Information, including (but not limited to) non-personally identifying information, which we may obtain from you or from other sources.

In addition, we may use your Personal Information to send you notice about, or invitations to, upcoming events in the collecting area in which you've made a purchase and to otherwise correspond with you about products, services, companies and events sponsored by us and others that we think might interest you. You may opt-out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the Opt-In and Opt-Out section above.

We also may provide visitors an opportunity to receive offers from other entities that provide services and products that we think might be of interest to you. However, we will not transfer your contact information to any unaffiliated third party for the third party's marketing purposes unless you expressly direct us to do so. If you change your mind and no longer want to receive third party promotions, follow the instructions to opt out in the Opt-In and Opt-Out section above.

We may analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, the Sites and emails, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate.

_Sharing of Personal Information and Sites’ Usage Information with others_

Paddle8 does not sell, lease or give your Personal Information to any other company absent your consent.

We do not store or share credit card information.

_Service Providers_

We may use third party partners to help operate the Sites and deliver our products and Services, and may share your information with service providers and other third parties that provide products or Services for or through the Sites or for our business (such as Sites or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, email service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf). These third party partners will be obligated to protect your confidential information.

_Aggregate Statistics_

We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, the Sites and emails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user.

_Legally Compelled Disclosures_

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required or permitted by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information in connection with investigations or when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the Sites, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

_Business Transfer_

Paddle8 regards its databases of customer information as a valuable asset. In the event that Paddle8, or substantially all of our assets, are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, such databases containing Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets. In using the Services you consent to such transfer of your Personal Information.

_Your Access to Your Personal Information_

You may review and edit the Personal Information that is stored on the Sites (e.g., your passwords and other contact information) by emailing privacy@paddle8.com. We will send you a copy of the Personal Information we have on file in your user account, if any. You may send us new or updated information at any time. We will endeavor to respond to your request to access, update or delete your information as soon as practicable. We may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information.

_Security_

Paddle8 will take reasonable steps to protect the security and integrity of all Personal Information provided to the Sites, including making your sensitive information available to our employees and agents on a need-to-know basis. However, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.

If you contact us by email, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by this method in transit.

You may be able to create an account on the Sites with a username and password. Passwords are encrypted and Paddle8 policies preclude access to passwords by anyone at Paddle8 or its service providers except on a need-to-know basis. If you do create a username and password, you are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you shall be responsible for any access to or use of the Sites by you or any person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you, and whether or not such person or entity is your employee or agent. You agree to (a) immediately notify Paddle8 of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. It is your sole responsibility to control the dissemination and use of your password, control access to and use of your account, and notify Paddle8 when you desire to cancel your account on the Sites. We will not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this provision.

We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission.

We may seek to notify you in the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your email address, we may notify you by email. You consent to our use of email as a means of such notification.

_Phishing_

It has become increasingly common for unauthorized individuals to send email messages to consumers by purporting to represent a legitimate company requesting that the consumer provide personal, often sensitive information. Sometimes, the domain name of the email address from which the email appears to have been sent, and the domain name of the Sites requesting such information, appears to be the domain name of a legitimate, trusted company. In reality, such sensitive information is received by an unauthorized individual to be used for purposes of identity theft. This illegal activity has come to be known as "phishing."

If you receive an email or other correspondence requesting that you provide any sensitive information (including your password or credit card information) via email or to a site that does not seem to be affiliated with the Sites, or that otherwise seems suspicious to you, please do not provide such information, and report such request to us at privacy@paddle8.com.

_Changes to this Privacy Policy_

Paddle8 reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of the Sites by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to the Sites. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by posting a notice on the Sites to sending you an email.

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, you may contact us at privacy@paddle8.com. You may also send mail to us with any comments, questions or concerns at:

Paddle8, Inc.  
30 Cooper Square, 4th Floor  
New York, New York 10003  
Attn: Web Master 

Last Modified: November 14, 2013
